export const data = [
    {
        question: "Which team won the 23/24 Premier League title?",
        option1: "Arsenal",
        option2: "Liverpool",
        option3: "Manchester City",
        option4: "Aston Villa",
        ans: 3,


    },
    {
        question: "Who was the top scorer in the 23/24 Premier League season?",
        option1: "Erling Haaland",
        option2: "Mohammed Salah",
        option3: "Ollie Watkins",
        option4: "Cole Palmer",
        ans: 1,


    },
    {
        question: "Who is the all time leading goalscorer in Premier League history?",
        option1: "Alan Shearer",
        option2: "Wayne Rooney",
        option3: "Harry Kane",
        option4: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        ans: 1,


    },
    {
        question: "Who has the most assists in Premier League history?",
        option1: "Kevin De Bruyne",
        option2: "Cesc Fabregas",
        option3: "Wayne Rooney",
        option4: "Ryan Giggs",
        ans: 4,

    },
    {
        question: "Who had the most clean sheets in the 23/24 Premier League season?",
        option1: "Ederson de Moraes",
        option2: "Nick Pope",
        option3: "David Raya",
        option4: "Emiliano Martinez",
        ans: 3,

    },
    {
        question: "Who has the most appearances in Premier League history?",
        option1: "James Milner",
        option2: "Gareth Barry",
        option3: "Frank Lampard",
        option4: "Ryan Giggs",
        ans: 2,

    },
    {
        question: "Which player had the most assists in the 23/24 Premier League season?",
        option1: "Kevin De Bruyne",
        option2: "Ollie Watkins",
        option3: "Cole Palmer",
        option4: "Morgan Gibbs-White",
        ans: 2,

    },
    {
        question: "Which player has the most passes in Premier League history?",
        option1: "Jordan Henderson",
        option2: "Kyle Walker",
        option3: "Gareth Barry",
        option4: "Ryan Giggs",
        ans: 1,

    },
    {
        question: "Which player has hit the woodwork the most in Premier League history?",
        option1: "Kevin De Bruyne",
        option2: "Sergio Aguero",
        option3: "Robin Van Persie",
        option4: "Harry Kane",
        ans: 3,

    },
    {
        question: "Which team has won the most Premier League titles ever?",
        option1: "Liverpool",
        option2: "Blackburn Rovers",
        option3: "Chelsea",
        option4: "Manchester United",
        ans: 4,

    },
]